If Mary alice was having some sort of crisis,we'd have known.
如果Mary alice有什么不对劲 我们应该会知道的
She lives 50 feet away, for god's sakes.
天晓得，她住的离我们不过50英尺
Gabby, the woman killed herlf.
Gabby, 她结束了自己的生命
Something must have been going on.
肯定有事情发生
Every time I'm around that man, he tries to grab my ass.
我每次遇见他，他都想摸我的屁股
I made over $200,000 doing business with him last year.
去年我和他做了超过20万美元的生意
If he wants to grab your ass, you let him.
如果他想摸你就让他摸吧
Why aren't you happy?
你为什么不开心？
Turns out I wanted all the wrong things.
结果证明我所要的东西都没用
What's that?
这是什么？
Oh, Mary Alice, what did you do?
哦，Mary Alice，你究竟干了什么？
An odd thing happens when we die.
我们死去以后就会有奇怪的事情发生
Our senses vanish.
我们没有感觉
Taste, touch, smell, and sound become a distant memory,
味觉、触觉、嗅觉和听觉 成为遥远的回忆
but our sight --
但是我们的视觉
ah, our sight expands,
啊，我们的视野开阔了
and we can suddenly see the world we've left behind so clearly.
我们能把被我们扔在身后的这个世界看清楚
Of course, most of what's visible to the dead could also be seen by the living,
当然，死人能看见的世界 活人也能看清楚
if they'd only take the time to look.
他们只是不愿意花时间去看而已
Like my friend Gabrielle.
就像我的朋友Gabrielle
I should have seen how unhappy she was, but I didn't.
我过去应该看出来她有多么不开心 但是我没有
I only saw her clothes from Paris...
我只看见了她的法国时装
and her platinum jewelry...
她的白金首饰
and her brand-new diamond watch.
和她崭新的钻石手表
Had I looked closer,
如果我看得更仔细
I'd have seen that Gabrielle was a drowning woman
我就会看出Gabrielle是个快溺毙的女人
desperately in search of a life raft.
绝望的在寻找生命的木筏
Luckily for her, she found one.
幸运的事，她找到了
Of course, Gabrielle only saw her young gardener
当然，Gabrielle只是找到了她年轻的园丁
as a way to infuse her life with a little excitement.
给她的生活中注入新鲜血液
But now she was about to discover just how exciting her life could get.
但是现在她想尝试一下
究竟她的生活可以有多精彩
Damn it.
该死!
Come on, come on, come on! Hurry up! Let's go!
快点，快点，快点！ 赶紧！快走！
Come on, come on!
快点，快点！
Where are the rest of my clothes?
我还有衣服呢？
I'll find them. Just get out.
我会找到的，赶快出去
Where?
去哪？
- Out the window.
- 窗户外面
What?
什么？
Go, go, go, go, go!
快走，快走！
Hi, honey. You're home early.
你好，亲爱的，你回来得真早
My meeting got canceled.
我的会议取消了
Didn't you take a shower this morning?
你今天早上不是已经洗过澡了吗？
I, uh, I just finished a workout.
我，呃，我刚刚锻炼完身体
Where's John?
John在哪里?
John?
Yeah. That's his truck out front.
是啊，外面有他的除草机
Gabrielle was panicked.
Gabrielle惊慌失措
She knew if her husband discovered her secret,
她知道如果他丈夫发现了她的秘密
she would feel the full force of his wrath.
她将在他的震怒中万劫不复
Hey, mr. Solis.
你好，Solis 先生
Hey, John, take care of that ficus yet?
你好，John, 那棵树弄好了吗？
- I'll get to it as soon as I'm done here.
- 我一忙完这个就去照料
All right.
好吧
- But she was quickly reminded that...
- 但是她很快想起来……
Yeah, sure.
好的
- what Carlos couldn't see...
- Carlos看不见的地方……
No problem.
没问题
Couldn't hurt her.
影响不了她
Episode 2
第2集
Ah, but underneath
啊，幕后谜情
The peaceful facade of Wisteria Lane had recently been shattered,
最近Wisteria Lane看似宁静的生活被打破了
first by my suicide...
首先是我的自杀
and then by the discovery of...
然后是发现了
a note among my belongings that suggested a suspicious reason for my desperate act.
遗物中的一个纸条 暗示了我自杀的一个可能的原因
My friends gathered to discuss its implications.
我的朋友们聚在一起 讨论它暗含的意义
I think we should give it to Paul.
我认为我们应该把它交给Paul
He's still mourning, Susan. He'll probably freak out.
Susan，他仍然沉浸在悲痛中 他很有可能失去理智
It doesn't matter. She was his wife. He deserves to have all the facts.
没有关系，她是他的老婆 他理应知道所有的事实真相
Well, we could do it gently.
我们可以做得巧妙一点
We could tell him about it over coffee and pastry.
我们可以在闲聊的时候告诉他
That would be fun.
那会很有意思
"Paul, we have proof your wife killed herself
“Paul，我们有证据证明你妻子的自杀
over some deep, dark secret. Another bear claw?"
有一些幕后的秘密。又一个晴天霹雳？”
We could always call the police.
我们也许可以报警
Maybe it's just some sort of sick joke.
也许这只是捉弄人的
Well, if it was a joke, it was in very poor taste.
如果这是个玩笑，那也太没水平了
No, this was serious. I know it was.
No, this was serious. I know it was. 不，这应该不是玩笑，我知道的
We got to find out what was going on.
我们要去找到事实真相
Let's say we do. There's a chance we're not going to like what we find.
看看我们该怎么办 有可能真相并不那么令人开心
Well, isn't it worse to be in the dark?
但是，那也比藏在地下要好呀？
I mean, imagining she did all these horrible things.
我是说，如果她真的做了这些恐怖的事情。
It's the age-old question, isn't it?
这是个老掉牙的问题，不是吗？
How much do we really want to know about our neighbors?
我们到底希望多么深入的 去了解我们的邻居？
My friends were right to be concerned.
朋友们的话是值得考虑的
They knew that every family has its secrets,
他们知道每个家庭都有自己的秘密
and as my son and husband could have told them,
正如我的儿子和丈夫可能会警戒她们的那样
you need to think carefully before digging them up.
在你把真相挖掘出来之前一定要想清楚
After talking for hours,
讨论了几个小时之后
my friends still hadn't agreed on what to do with the note.
朋友们仍然没有对如何处治这个纸条达成一致
So they decided to talk about it in the morning after a good night's rest.
因此她们决定先好好睡一觉 明天早上再讨论
But no one could sleep that night.
但是晚上她们谁也没有睡好
They each kept thinking of my suicide
每个人都在想我自杀的事情
and how terribly alone I must have felt.
在想我肯定是觉得非常非常的孤独
You see, loneliness was something my friends understood all too well.
看见了吗，孤独是我的朋友们感受最深的
It's okay. I'm up.
好了，我醒了
Good.
好
I have a question for you.
我有个问题
Do you remember when you proposed?
你还记得你向我求婚时的情景吗？
For god's sake --
看在上帝的份上……
We sat on skyline drive and drank a bottle of apple wine,
我们驱车沿着海边 喝了一瓶苹果香槟
and  when we finished it, you turned to me, and you said,
当我们喝完的时候， 你转向我，对我说
"if you marry me, Bree Mason,
“Bree Mason，如果你嫁给我
I promise to love you for the rest of my life."
我会今生今世永远爱你”
And even though I was engaged to Ty Grant, and even though my father didn't like you,
尽管我已经和Ty Grant订婚 尽管我爸爸不喜欢你
I said yes.
我还是答应嫁给你
That was a long time ago.
那是很久以前的事了
You're going to cancel the meeting with that divorce lawyer,
你要去取消和律师的会面
and we're going to find ourselves a marriage counselor.
然后去找一个婚姻顾问
- Bree -- - You promised.
- 你许过诺言。
All right.
好吧
Good.  I'm going to go, uh, make myself some warm milk.
好，我要去给自己准备一杯热牛奶
Would you like something to drink?
你想要点什么饮料吗？
Anything but apple wine.
只要不是苹果香槟就行
Susan awoke that night alone and parched,
那天晚上Susan独自醒来 饥渴万分
but as she gazed out her window,
当她朝窗外看的时候
she saw the tall drink of water she needed to quinch her thirst.
她看到了可以解渴的一大杯水
"dear diary, Mike doesn't even know I'm alive."
“亲爱的日记，Mike 甚至不知道我还存在着”
Shut up.
闭嘴
If you want to date him, you're going to have to ask him out.
如果你想和他约会，就要喊他出来
I keep hoping he'll ask me out.
我一直希望他采取主动
How's that going?
结果呢？
Shouldn't you be making brownies for your nerdy friends?
你怎么还不为你的狐朋狗友们准备巧克力蛋糕？
I can't find the measuring cup. Have you seen it?
我找不到量杯了，你有看到吗？
The measuring cup?
量杯？
Yeah.
是啊
I -- well, it's -- it's got to be here somewhere. Just keep looking.
我，哦，原来一直放这的，再找找看。
I know you're awake.
我知道你没睡
I know you're a jerk.
我知道你是个杂碎
Dinner with Tanaka ran long. I'm sorry.
和Tanaka吃晚饭时间长了点 对不起
You know, Carlos, I didn't marry you so I could have dinner by myself six times a week.
Carlos, 你知道，我嫁给你并不是为了一周有六天都独自吃晚饭
You know how bored I was today?
你知道今天我有多闷？
I came this close to actually cleaning the house.
我闷到居然彻彻底底的打扫了一次房子
Don't be that way. I got you a gift.
别这样 我给你买了份礼物
Nope. No, no, no, no.
不行，不行
You're not going to buy your way out of this one.
你别指望这就把我给打发了
It's a good gift.
很棒的礼物
Is that white gold?
是白金的吗？
Yeah. Put it on...
是的，戴上它……
and then make love to me.
然后和我做爱
I'm not in the mood.
我没心情
But we could stay up and talk.
我们可以不睡觉，聊聊天
When a man buys a womaexpensive jewelry,
当一个男人给女人买了非常昂贵的首饰
there are many things he may want in return for future reference,
他希望得到很多回报
conversation ain't one of them.
但不是聊天
- Hey, that was a joke.
- 嗨，只是开个玩笑
Yeah, right.
是，没错。
I can't fix it unless you tell me.
如果你不告诉我 我是不会放过你的
It's not exciting anymore, Carlos.
Carlos，生活不再那么有意思了
So what am I supposed to do?
你想让我怎么做
I don't know.
我不知道
Be the way you used to be.
和过去的你一样
Surprise me. Take my breath away.
给我惊喜，让我出乎意料
Okay.
好吧
Hey, Susan.
－你好，Susan －Mike
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I didn't realize anybody was going to be out here. I just sort of rolled out of bed.
我想可能没人会在这 所以只裹了条毛毯
I'm sure you look fine.
你看起来很好
Oh, Bongo, stop.
哦，Bongo，别叫了
Sorry, uh... he scares easy.
对不起，呃，它很容易被吓倒
No, it-- it's fine.
没，没关系
I-I get it. I didn't mean to disturb you.
知道了，我没想要打扰你
I'll see you later.
再见
Do you want to have dinner with me?
你想和我一起吃晚饭吗？
Just the two of us?
就我们俩？
Well... and Julie.
呃，还有Julie
It's a thing we do when somebody new moves into the neighborhood,
当有新邻居搬来时
we invite them over for a home-cooked meal. Sort of a tradition.
我们会邀请他们来家里吃一顿晚餐 是老传统
I thought you said you were a lousy cook.
我记得你说过你厨艺不精
Well, I order takeout.
那么，我叫外面
Oh, you invite them over for home cooking and give them takeout.
哦，你邀请别人来家里吃饭 然后叫外卖
Yeah, it's -- it's -- it's sort of a new tradition.
是的，这，这是一种新的习俗
I'm working out the kinks.
我的突发奇想
I'll tell you what -- how about I cook and you guys come over to my place?
这样吧，我来做饭 你们来我家吃饭，怎么样？
Great.
好极了
Friday night at 6:00?
星期五晚上六点？
I'll be there.
我会准时到的
All right. Come on
好的，走吧
Bye, Bongo.
再见，Bongo
Julie!
Mike Delfino just invited us to dinner friday night.
Mike Delfino刚刚邀请了我们星期五晚上去吃晚饭
He did? Cool.
是吗？太酷了
But only I'm going, because you're going to come down with something semi-serious
但我要一个人去 因为你得了比较严重的病
that requires bed rest and fluids.
需要好好休息和打吊针
Julie was glad Susan was rekindling her love life.
Julie 很高兴Susan重新开始了她的爱情生活
Of course, she was unaware of her mother's recent track record with fire.
当然，她没有意识到她妈妈最近纵火的劣迹
It's all gone --
都过去了……
everything my ex-husband worked for all those years.
我的前夫这些年的辛苦
Gone.
都白费了
Well, don't worry about clothing.
好了，别担心衣服了
I already started a collection from people in the neighborhood.
我已经开始去邻里搜集一些衣服了
What? I don't want to wear other people's old crap.
什么？我可不想穿别人的旧衣服
Edie, you can be homeless, or you can be ungracious. You really can't afford to be both.
Edie，你可以无家可归， 也可以穿着寒碜，如果两样兼备可够你受的
That reminds me -- my insurance check still hasn't come yet.
这提醒了我 我的保险支票还没到呢
Can I stay with you for a few more weeks?
我能在这多住几个星期吗？
Of course. What kind of christian would I be if I denied shelter to a friend in need?
当然，如果我拒绝帮助处在困境中的朋友 还算什么基督徒呢？
Oh, look, here's something we can salvage.
哦，看这个，我们可以变废为宝
Your measuring cup.
你的量杯
We can just scrape off the burnt part, and it'll look good as new.
我们将烧坏的部分刮掉 就会和新的一样了
That's not my cup. Mine was plastic.
那不是我的杯子 我的是塑料制的
Well,  how did it get in here?
那它是怎么到这来的？
I don't know. Who cares?
我不知道 这有什么大不了的？
Now, would you put that down and start looking for jewelry?
现在你能把那玩意放下 然后开始找珠宝了吗？
Dr. Albert Goldfein was the most accomplished marriage counselor in the city.
Albert Goldfein医生是城里最有经验的婚姻顾问
He had dealt with problems ranging from substance abuse
他处理过无数的问题婚姻 从吸毒
to infidelity
到婚外情
to domestic violence.
到家庭暴力
Yes, dr. Goldfine thought he had seen it all,
是的，Albert Goldfein医生以为他了解了婚姻百态
and then he met the Van de Kamps.
直到他遇见了Van de Kamps
Hi. I'm Bree, and this is my husband Rex...
你好，我是Bree，这是我丈夫Rex……
and I brought you some homemade potpourri.
我给你带了一些自制的香花
The answer is yes.
你猜得没错
You're about to make a fortune off of us.
你又要从我们身上赚大钱了
Guys, I'm very --
家伙们，我非常……
Sit in your seats.
坐到座位上去
I am not going to tell you again!
我不想再说一遍了
Buckle up!
扣上安全带！
I mean it, so help me, I will --
我很认真，拜托，我要……
Crap!
该死！
Licenses, registration, ma'am.
请出示驾照和登记证
Ma'am, you know why I pulled you over?
夫人，你知道我为什么拦你吗？
I have a theory.
愿闻其详
The kids are jumping up and down. They should be sitting, wearing their seat belts.
这些小家伙爬上爬下 他们应该坐好，并系上安全带
I don't let them -- they don't even listen to me. It's very frustrating.
我让他们别这样 他们根本不听，真没办法
Well, you have to find a way to control them. After all, that's your job.
你要想办法制住他们 不过，那是你的工作
Though he'd been a policeman for six years,
尽管他已经干了六年的警察
officer Hayes had never found himself in a truly dangerous situation.
Hayes发现他这次的处境才真正很危险
Then again, he had never before told a woman how to raise her children.
他以前从没告诉过一个女人 该怎样去管教孩子
Are you saying I'm a bad mother?
你是说我是个失败的母亲？
Ma'am, you need to get back in your car, please.
夫人，请回到车里
I have no help. My husband's always away on business.
没有人帮我 我丈夫总是在外忙生意
I'm going to have to ask you to step back now.
我必须警告你立刻回到车上
My babysitter joined the witness relocation program.
我的管家换工作了
I haven't slept through the night in six years,
六年来我晚上从没好好睡过觉
and for you to stand there and judge me...
而你却站在这儿 对我评头论足
I'm not going to give you a ticket.
我不给你开罚单了
I'm just going to let you off with a warning.
只是给你个警告
I accept your apology.
我接受你的道歉
Buckle up.
系好安全带
Mrs. Solis.
Solis 夫人
Hello, Jonathan.
你好， Jonathan
Well, this is my room.
嗯，这是我的房间
Sorry about the mess.
很抱歉，这一团糟
Ah, don't worry about it.
啊，没关系
You just missed my mom. Friday she coaches my little sister's soccer team.
我妈妈刚刚来过 星期五她要给我妹妹的足球队担任教练
Oh, yes. I heard that.
哦，是的，我听你说过了
Um, John, we need to talk about what happened the other day.
呃，John，我们要谈谈前几天发生的事
Mr. Solis isn't starting to catch on, is he?
Solis先生开始怀疑你了，是吗？
No, no, he doesn't have a clue, god love him.
不，没有，上帝保佑 他没什么证据
It's just that when you come over to garden, you might actually have to garden.
只是当你去花园时 你应该真的是在干园艺活
Great. You're breaking up with me
好极了，你想和我分手
in my own bedroom.
在我的卧室里
No, no, no. I'm not dumping you.
不，不是，我并没有想抛弃你
Lately you've been the only thing keeping me going.
这些天来只有你才能让我开心
It's just we can't do it at my house anymore.
只是我们不能再在我家里做爱了
So, then, where do you want to do it?
那你想在哪做？
Well, what time does your mom get back from soccer practice?
你妈妈从足球比赛回来还有多久？
Mrs. Solis.
Solis夫人
Better hurry. We don't have a lot of time.
最好快点 我们没那么多时间
And so there's just the four of us.
这就是我们一家四口
My older son Andrew is 16, Danielle is 15, and --
大儿子Andrew 16岁， Danielle 15岁
I don't need to see pictures. Bree,
Bree，我不需要看这些照片
you've spent most of the hour engaging in small talk.
你大部分时间都在说些鸡毛蒜皮的小事
Oh, have I?
哦，是吗？
Yes. Rex has been very vocal about his issues.
是的，Rex 对他的问题畅所欲言
Don't you want to discuss your feelings about your marriage?
你难道不想谈谈你对婚姻的感受吗？
Doc, um... this is the thing you got to know about Bree --
医生，呃，你必须了解Bree……
she doesn't like to talk about her feelings.
她不愿意谈论她的感情
To be honest, it's hard to know if s has any.
老实说，很难知道她是否还有感情
Does she feel anger, rage, ecstasy?
她有过生气，勃然大怒 或者欣喜若狂吗？
Who knows?
谁知道？
She's always pleasant,
她总是显得很开心
and I can't tell you how annoying that is.
我无法描述这会让人多么恼火
Whatever she feels, it's so far below the surface, no one can see it.
不管她感觉如何， 都隐藏在心里，没有人能知道
I feel like she's using all these...
我感到她一直在用这些……
What?
什么？
Uh, I'm sorry.
呃，很抱歉
Would you like to respond to what Rex just said?
你愿意谈谈刚刚Rex所说的吗？
Is there some truth there?
他说的是真的吗？
Do you use housework as a way to disengage emotionally?
你用家务活去掩盖你的感情？
Of course not.
当然不是
Ah. This is great.
啊，这太棒了
I've got tons of homework tonight.
今天晚上我要大干一场了
It's so easy to concentrate after sex.
做爱之后干什么都容易集中精力
I'm glad I could help. Education is very important.
很高兴我能帮上忙 教育很重要
Oh, I got something for you.
哦，有样东西要给你
I was going to give it to you next time I mowed your lawn,
我本来打算下次去除草的时候给你
but since you're here...
不过既然你来了
Oh, it's a rose.
噢，是朵玫瑰
It's not just any rose.
这不是普通的玫瑰
Look at all the petals. There's no floss. It's perfect.
看看所有这些花瓣， 都没有瑕疵，它很完美
Oh, John.
哦，John
Just like you.
就像你一样
The truth hit her like a thunderbolt.
事实像雷电一样击中了她
I spent days looking for just the right one. I finally found it.
我花了好多天去找最完美的一朵 终于找到了
For John, this was no longer a meaningless little affair.
对John来说 这不再是轻描淡写的风流韵事
Gabrielle could now clearly see he was falling in love with her.
Gabrielle 明显的看出来 他已经爱上了她
It's just beautiful.
它很美
I...
我……
I got to go.
我得走了
G oodbye.
再见
So what are we having?
你抱的是什么？
Uh, well, I talked to Julie, and -- thanks. And she suggested rib eye steaks.
呃，我问过Julie 非常感谢，她建议做肋排
She said that's your favorite.
她说那是你最喜欢吃的
Oh, yeah, I love my steak.
哦，是的，我喜欢吃排骨
Hi, Mike. Susan.
你好, Mike，Susan
Hey, I'm sorry about your house. How you holding up?
嗨，对你房子的事我很遗憾 你拿的什么？
All right, I guess.
好吧，我猜猜
Oh, is somebody having a party?
有人要开个派对吗？
No, Susan's just throwing me one of her traditional welcome-to-the-neighborhood dinners,
不，Susan 邀请我参加她的传统的欢迎新邻居的晚餐
only I'm cooking...
由我来做饭
and having it at my house.
在我家
Ha ha. Traditional, huh? I didn't get one.
哈哈，传统的，嗯？ 我怎么没有被邀请过？
Oh, it's sort of a new tradition.
哦，是新的传统
Well, it won't be anything fancy. Just a little home cooking.
哦，不会有什么太新奇的 只是在家做些吃的
That sounds so good.
听起来不错
Susan suddenly had an awful feeling in the pit of her stoma...
Susan突然觉得胃里非常不舒服
I've been having nothing but fast food lately.
最近我除了快餐还没吃过别的
As if she was watching an accident in slow motion.
好像她正在看一次事故的慢镜头
She knew it would happen, but was powerless to stop it.
她知道会发生什么事 却无能为力
Edie, would you like to join us for dinner?
Edie，你愿意参加我们的晚餐吗？
Oh, that's so sweet.
哦，太好了
No, I don't want to intrude. Three's a crowd.
不过我不想打扰 三个人不太好
No, it's not like that. I mean, Susan's bringing Julie.
不是那样的 我是说，Susan会带Julie来
Yeah, it's not like that.
是的，不是那样的
The more, the merrier.
人越多越开心
- Well, this will be fun.
- 那就太好了
All right.
好吧
- Tomorrow night.We'll eat at 6:00.
- 明天晚上，六点开始
Great.
好极了
Oh, and, Susan...
－对了， Susan
Yeah.
什么事？
This will make up for the dinner that you never threw me.
这可以弥补你欠我的那顿晚饭了
Right. Ha ha.
是的，呵
Should I have told her we were having steak?
我是不是该告诉她我们要吃肋排？
She's not, like, a vegetarian or something, is she?
她应该不会是个素食主意者 是吗？
Oh, no, no.
哦，不会，不会
No, edie's definitely a carnivore.
不，Edi绝对是个肉食动物
Here's, um...
这里是，嗯……
Here's what I pulled for Edie.
这是我为Edie准备的
I should warn you that most of the clothes in there aren't that stylish.
我要告诉你 大部分衣服都不是那么过时
Oh, don't worry about it. Edie's a beggar now,
哦，没关系 Edie现在是个小乞丐
which means she can'be a chooser.
就是说她不能挑三拣四的
Of course, we don't have to add salt to the wound.
当然我们也没必要 雪上加霜
Listen, I was just getting dinner ready.
哦，我要去做晚饭了
Say no more.
不用招呼我了
- I'll get out of your hair.
- 我不耽误你做事了
No, no.
没关系
By the way, was that you I saw getting pulled over by a policeman?
对了，那天我看见有个人被警察拦下了，是你吗？
Yeah, the boys were acting up in the car,
是啊，小家伙们在汽车里捣乱
and I couldn't get them to sit down.
我没办法让他们老实呆一会
Young boys can be so willful.
小孩子们就是这样任性
I try everything.
我什么招都使了
I scream, I threaten, I reason, I beg. Nothing works.
大叫，威胁，讲道理，请求 但都不管用
I don't know if it's because they're too young and they don't understand,
我不知道是不是因为他们太小 听不懂我的意思
or if they're just getting some perverse joy out of testing me.
他们不断的挑战我从中取乐
My mother used to have the worst time with me in the car,
我妈妈过去也总为我在车里捣乱而头疼不已
so one time when I was acting up, she stopped
有一次我不听话的时候 她停下车
and left me on the side of the road, and she drove off.
把我扔在路边 然后把车开走了
You're kidding.
你在开玩笑吧
Oh, she came back immediately,
不过，她很快就回来了
but I never misbehaved in the car again.
从那以后我就老实了
You should try that.
你也可以试试
Mrs. Huber, I could never leave my kids by the side of the road.
Huber夫人，我不可能把我的孩子丢在路边
When it comes to discipline, sometimes you must be creative.
在教育孩子守规矩的时候 你要有些创意
My mother knew that. Smart lady.
我妈妈就懂得这一点 她是个聪明的母亲
Of course, she's in a home now,
当然，她现在已经不在人世了
and her mind has just turned to mush.
但她的想法确实很管用
Well, like I said, I should go back and get dinner ready.
我差点忘了，我要回去准备晚饭了
Oh, right, right.
好吧
- Goodbye.
- 再见
Goodbye.
再见
Susan, have you been able to find old clothes for Edie?
Susan，你能给Edie找一些旧衣服吗？
She has nothing to wear.
她没的穿了
I thought that was the look she was going for.
我还以为她故意穿成那样呢
Oh, Susan.
哦, Susan
Edie may be trash, but she's still a human being.
Edie may be trash, but she's still a human being. Edie也许善乏可陈 但还是人性未泯
Zach? Is your dad home?
Zach？你爸爸在家吗？
I need to talk to him.
我需要和他谈谈
- Hey, Paul.
- 嗨, Paul
Hey.
嗨
Hope I'm not interrupting.
希望我没有打扰到你
Actually, I was getting ready to go somewhere.
事实上，我是在准备搬家
I just wanted to come by and say hello, you know,
我只是想过来打个招呼
see how you guys a doing.
看看你们现在过得怎么样
We're trying to move on. It's been pretty tough.
我们要搬家了 很麻烦的
Yeah, I could only imagine.
我能想到
I mean, not knowing why Mary Alice...
我是说，不知道Mary Alice为什么……
Why what?
什么为什么？
Why she did it. Oh, here, let me help you.
为什么那么做 让我来帮你
I've got it, I've got it.
我自己来，我自己来
I'm sorry if I upset you.
非常抱歉，如果我让你心烦意乱了
Can I be frank?
我能直说吗？
Of course.
当然可以
I don't care what her reasons were.
我不在乎到底为什么
Maybe she was depressed, maybe she was bored.
也许她很消沉 也许她厌倦了生活
It doesn't matter.
这些都不重要
She abandoned her husband and her son, and I'll never forgive her.
但她弃她丈夫和儿子而去 我永远不会原谅她
As I watched Ssusan, I couldn't help feeling sorry for her.
我看着Susan的时候 忍不住为她感到悲哀
She wanted so much to know why I did it...
她那么的想知道 我为什么……
Why I killed myself.
为什么要自杀
It's not enough to want the truth.
但光是想知道还不够
You must know where to look for it.
你必须清楚在哪儿能够找到事实
And the truth is elusive, because it knows where to hide.
但事实并不是那么显而易见的 因为它清楚该隐藏在哪
Hello, Julie.
你好，Julie
I talked to your mom about donating some clothes for Edie.
我跟你妈妈说过 给Edie捐一些衣服
She's at mrs. Van de Kamp's,
她在Van de Kamp夫人那里
but I'll see if she left some stuff upstairs.
我去楼上看看她有没有什么可捐的
I-I was, um, just admiring your new measuring cup.
我，我，呃，只是在看看你的新量杯
Yeah, we lost ours.
是啊，旧的丢了
Really?
是吗？
So I couldn't find the clothes. I'm sorry.
我找不到衣服 很抱歉
That's okay.
没关系
If you want me to keep looking...
如果你希望我再找找
No, you've done more than enough, truly.
不用了，你已经给我帮了很多忙了 真的
Bree, Rex just called. He won't be able to meet you here today.
Bree，Rex刚打来电话 他今天不能来这和你见面了
Apparently, there was an emergency at the hospital.
显然是医院有急救任务
Oh. Well, I wish he had called me.
哦，好的 我倒希望他给我打电话
He suggested perhaps you'd like to meet with me by yourself.
他建议说 也许你愿意单独和我谈谈
You've been very quiet in our joint sessions.
你在我们的会面过程中 一直聊得很少
What?
什么？
Oh -- oh, no, thank you. I-I have some things that I-I need to do today.
哦，不用，谢谢你 我，我今天有些事要处理
You -- you sure?
你，你确定？
Uh, yeah. I'm sure.
呃，是的，确定。
Dr. Goldfine, there is something you can do for me.
Goldfine医生，有件事我想你能帮我
What's that?
什么事？
Take off your coat.
脱下外套
So now you're taking Julie on the dinner date with Mike?
所以现在你打算 带Julie一起去和Mike吃晚餐？
Yeah, well, if Edie's going to be there, I'm going to need emotional support.
是的，我想，如果Edie也在哪儿， 我需要情感上的支持者
I can't believe she wormed her way in.
简直不敢相信 她也想插一竿子
- How did you let her do that?
- 你居然会允许她那样做
I don't know.
我不知道
I was going to take her out at the knees, but it all happened so fast.
我正盘算怎么把她打发走 但一切发生得太快了
Well, you know what you need to do.
好吧，你知道该怎么做
You need to get there early, spend a little time with Mike before the little barracuda gets there.
你要早点去，赶在那个小娼妇之前 和Mike多呆一会
That's a good idea.
好主意
Edie will get there at 5:45, which means her breasts will arrive at 5:30,
Edie应该5：45到那儿， 也就是说她5：30可能就到了
so I should shoot for 5:00.
而我在5：00就到那儿
That a girl.
你算得真准
I'm just going to take these upstairs.
我正要把这些东西拿到楼上去
I'm going to keep my one little bag and go home.
我正准备提着我的小包包回家
That is a beautiful rose. Where did you get it?
非常漂亮的玫瑰 哪儿弄到的
Oh, John gave it to me.
哦，John送给我的
John? Your gardener? He gave you a rose?
John？你的园丁？ 他送你玫瑰花？
Yes.
是的
I am having some new bushes planted outside,
我在外面新开辟了一块园地
and he gave me that as a color palette.
他送花给我做些点缀
Sure is beautiful, isn't it?
确实非常漂亮 不是吗？
Yes, it is.
是的
I'm sure Freud would not approve of this.
我肯定弗洛伊德肯定不赞成这样
Oh, who cares what he thinks?
哦，谁会在乎他怎么想？
I took psychology in college. We learned all about Freud.
我大学修的是心理学 我们完全了解弗洛伊德
A miserable human being.
一个悲惨的人
What makes you say that?
你为什么这么说？
Well, think about it --
哦，提起这个……
he grew up in the late 1800s. There were no appliances back then.
他生活在19世纪晚期的环境中 那时候没什么设备可利用
His mother had to do everything by hand,
他妈妈只好亲手打理所有的事情
just backbreaking work from sunup to sundown,
从早到晚辛勤劳作
not to mention the countless other sacrifices she probably had to make to take care of her family.
更不用说为了家庭 她可能做出了无数的牺牲
And what does he do?
他做什么了？
He grows up and becomes famous peddling a theory
他长大了 提出了一个沽名钓誉的理论
that the problems of most adults
说什么大部分成人的问题
can be traced back to something awful their mother has done.
可以追溯到他妈妈所做的一些不好的事情
She must have felt so betrayed.
她肯定感到自己被背叛的
He saw how hard she worked.
他知道她工作辛苦
He saw what she did for him.
也知道她为他所做的一切
Did he even ever think to say "thank you"?
他想过要说声谢谢吗？
I doubt it.
我表示怀疑
There you go.
给你
Just so you know, many of Freud's theories have been discredited.
正如你知道的那样 很多弗洛伊德的理论都是名不副实的
Good.
很好
Boys, I am not going to tell you again -- sit. I mean it.
小家伙们，我不会再重复了 坐下，我是认真的
I am serious.
我真的生气了
You boys are going to be in so much trouble if you don't sit back in those seats.
你们这些臭屁，捅了这么多漏子 如果你们再不回到座位上
For the first time, Lynette could see this was not the innocent play of children.
这是第一次 Lynette感觉到孩子们不是在闹着玩
She was being challenged.
而是在向她发出挑战
So she decided it was time to get creative.
她决定是时候来点创意了
Out. Can't behave, you heard me, you cannot ride.
下车，你们不乖 我警告过你们，你们不能坐在车上了
You, out.
你，下车
- Where's mom going?
- 妈妈要去哪儿？
I don't know.
我不知道
Mommy's a genius.
妈妈是个天才
5, 6
- alright.
- 好了
I will be right back.
我现在就开回去
Boys?
孩子们？
If you're hiding, you've got to stop now, 'cause mommy doesn't think it's funny!
如果你们躲起来了 现在该出来了 因为妈妈不觉得这很好玩
Oh, excuse me.
哦，对不起
I'm sorry. I'm looking for my boys. Three boys with red hair.
很抱歉，我正在找我的孩子们 三个红头发的男孩
- Have you seen them?
- 你看到他们了吗？
Yeah. I also saw you drive away and leave them.
是的，我还看见你把他们扔在路边然后开走了
I know. I was just trying to scare them into behaving.
我知道，我只是想吓唬一下他们 让他们变乖一点
Did you see where they went?
你看见他们去哪儿了吗？
Yeah, yeah, yeah. They're in my kitchen.
是的，看见了 他们在我的厨房里
Listen, uh, it seems to me that you have some anger management issues.
听着，呃，我觉得你的管理方式好像有点问题
I have four kids under the age of 6. I absolutely have anger management issues.
我有4个六岁以下的孩子 我当然要采用发怒式的管理方式
Yeah, well, I think you need to talk to somebody,
是的，我觉得你需要找个人聊聊
because abandoning your children is --
因为抛弃你的孩子们是……
Hey, I-I didn't abandon them. I came back.
嗨，我、我不是抛弃他们 我又回来了
I'm just saying it's not normal.
我只是说这很不正常
Well, my kids aren't normal,
是我的孩子们很不正常
and now I don't have time for this, lady, so --
现在我没时间讨论这个，夫人，那么……
boys, get out here!
孩子们，出来
No, I don't think they should go anywhere until you calm down.
不行，你不平静下来他们哪儿也不能去
- Get in the car.
- 回到车里
She's got cookies.
她给我们吃饼干
Well, bring them. We're leaving.
好，带上饼干，我们走了
- Oh, no, no. Stay put.
- 哦，不行，不行，呆在里面
I don't think so. Aah!
我不这么想，啊！
- Listen, lady, you and I are going to have a little talk.
- 听着，女士，你和我得好好谈谈
Leave my mommy alone!
放开我妈妈
Let go of me!
放开我
What's the matter with you?
你怎么回事？
Run, boys, run!
快跑，孩子们，快跑！
Son of a -- aah!
该死，啊！
You get back here!
你们回来
Boys, you're going to need to put on your --
孩子们，你们赶紧系上……
You come back here right now! Get back or I'm going to call social services!
你们赶快给我回来 要不然我就给社会服务机构打电话了
Oh, my god.
哦，天啊
Carlos, what have you done?
Carlos，你疯了吗？
I saw it when I drove by the dealership.
我路过车行的时候看见的
I thought, "Gabrielle would look so beautiful in this."
我在想：Gabrielle坐在车里看起来肯定会很潇洒
Cost me an arm and a leg.
我花了大价钱买的
It's got GPS navigation, 200-watt stereo system, rear parking --
GPS导航系统，200瓦的音响，倒车雷达……
Oh, my god, it's beautiful.
哦，天啊，帅呆了
So... did I take your breath away?
我让你出乎意料了吗？
Absolutely.
绝对
Is it the best gift you've ever gotten?
这是你收到的最好了礼物吗？
Gabrielle could see what this gesture had cost Carlos,
Gabrielle能看出来Carlos花了很大心思
so she responded the only way she knew how.
她只能用她所知道的唯一的方式来报答他
She had a feeling the truth would have been lost on her husband anyway.
她有一种感觉，不管怎么样 真理都掌握在她丈夫手里
After all,
毕竟
it's the rare man who understands the value of a single perfect rose.
很少有人能懂得珍惜一支玫瑰的价值
Oh, I hope you don't mind. I thought I'd come by early and help you set up.
希望你不要介意 我早点过来看看能不能帮上忙？
Hey, Susan.
嗨，Susan
Don't worry. Mike and I have got everything under control.
别担心，Mike和我把这里打点的很好
Bongo.
Bongo
I don't know why he barks at you.
我不明白它为什么总朝着你叫唤
Well, I wouldn't take it personally. Dogs are very sensitive.
我不会介意的，狗都是很敏感的
What's up, Bongo, huh?
怎么了?Bongo，嗯？
You never know what freaks them out, huh?
你永远都不会知道是什么惹恼了它们
In the distance, susan thought she heard a bell ring.
远远的，Susan觉得好像听到一声丧钟
Ooh, is it a strange noise, huh? What is it? A weird smell?
Ooh, is it a strange noise, huh? What is it? A weird smell? 哦，是什么响动还是别的？ 一种奇怪的味道？
Round one had started.
第一声钟响了
Look, all I'm saying is that this whole
听着，我想说的就是
"it takes two to mess up a marriage" theory is bull.
“一个巴掌拍不响”这个理论是狗屁
The problems that weave are because of her.
问题都出在她身上
That is not true, Rex.
不是这样的，Rex
All right, fine. What have I been doing for the past 20 years that's been so awful?
好吧，二十年来我做了什么不好的事情
You're not saying anything because I've been a great husband,
你什么都不说是因为我是一个完美的丈夫
and it kills you to admit that.
承认这一点会要你命
Rex, I'm curious --
Rex，我很好奇……
do you ever acknowledge the benefits of living with Bree?
你从没有意识过和Bree生活在一起的好处吗？
Huh?
嗯？
By your own admission, your home is always clean,
你自己也承认过你的家里总是很干净
your clothes are always freshly pressed. Sounds like a wonderful cook.
你的衣服总是熨的很平整 每天都有丰盛的饭菜
Despite her flaws, do you ever remember to say "thank you"?
先撇开她的缺点不谈 你有没有要说过一声谢谢
"Thank you"?
谢谢？
Yes.
是啊
Bongo! Bongo.Get down. Down.
Bongo! Bongo，下去
Go on. Unh-unh. Down.
走开，呃，下去
I'm sorry.
不好意思
So, um, who's the guy that lives across from mrs. Huber again?
呃，住在Huber夫人对面的那个人是谁呀？
Mm. That's mr. Mullen,
姆，是 Mullen先生
and just so you know, if he invites you in, you have to meet all of his pets.
都知道，如果他邀请你去他家 他会让你和他的所有宠物都打个招呼
That's okay. I love animals.
没问题，我喜欢动物
He's a taxidermist.
他专门搜集动物标本
Thanks for the warning.
谢谢你的提醒
Isn't mr. Mullen's brother your divorce attorney?
Mullen先生的哥哥是你的离婚律师吗？
Uh, yes. Yes, he was.
呃，是的，是他
Can I say something?
我能说点什么吗？
In my heart, I still believe that you and Carl are going to get back together.
从内心深处 我依然坚信你和Carl还会回到一起的
Really?
真的？
Oh, yeah, I-I've never seen two people more in love.
哦，是的，我，我从没看见像你们这么相爱的一对了
I mean, she's never going to find that kind of chemistry with another man. Never.
我是说，她再也没遇到过能和她产生化学反应的男人了 永远不会了
It was everything susan could do to keep a smile on her face.
现在Susan 所能做的就是保持住微笑了
Round two was under way, and she was already taking a beating.
第二声丧钟响了 她已经败了第一回合
- You know what, mrs. Britt?
- Britt夫人，你知道吗?
What edie hadn't counted on...
Edie没有料到
- Do you know who I always liked?
- 你知道我一起很喜欢谁吗?
Was Susan had someone else in her corner.
Susan还有一个同盟军.
Mr. Authwell -- your fourth husband.
Authwell先生，你的第四任丈夫
Oh, he was my second husband. I've only been married twice.
哦，他是第二任 我只结过两次婚
Twice?
两次？
You weren't married to the guy with all the tattoos that they took away in handcuffs?
你没有嫁给那个全身纹身 最后被铐走的那个家伙吗？
No, Julie, she wasn't married to Javier.
没有，Julie，她没有嫁给Javier
That was just one of her special friends.
那只是和她有特殊关系的朋友之一
I think we should change the subject. You know, unless you want to keep talking about it.
我想我们该换个话题 除非你想一直谈论这个
Bongo, get down.
Bongo, 下来
Wait, wait. Let -- let me show you something. Bongo.
等等，我给你们看点精彩的，Bongo
He loves that gravy.
它喜欢吃那个调味汁
While you were in there tossing the salad,
你们在准备沙拉的时候
I taught him something.
我教了它几招
Up.
上面
Susan was furious with Edie for using a dog to ingratiate herself with its owner.
Susan 觉得很生气 Edie利用一只狗去博取他主人的欢心
She was also furious with Mike for not seeing through this blatant maneuver.
她还生气Mike 没有识破她拙劣的伎俩
But mostly...
但是更多……
you know what? I'm going to go get the desserts.
这样吧，我去拿点甜点
She was furious with herself for not having thought of it first.
她在生自己的气 为什么没有提前考虑到这些
I can barely get him to sit.
我连驯服他坐下都很难
You are a good dog. You're the best dog ever. Yes, you are.
你是一只很棒的狗 最棒的，是的
Ha ha. I've never seen him walk on two legs.
哈哈，我从没见过它用两条腿走路
Well, he knows who to come to, doesn't he? He knows who to come to.
它知道该和谁亲，不是吗？ 它知道该跟谁亲热
Here's your dessert.
甜点来了
Thank you. Mmm. My, this looks yummy.
谢谢，姆，看起来非常好吃
Oh, look at that.
哦，快看
Looks like Bongo's finally warming up to Susan.
看起来好像Bongo终于喜欢上Susan了
Yeah, we just got off on the wrong foot. We're best buddies now.
是的，我们刚刚解除了误会 现在是最后的朋友了
Oh, what a good boy.
哦，多棒的狗狗
Bongo, are you okay?
Bongo, 你没事吧?
What's wrong with him?
它怎么了？
I don't know. I've never heard him make that sound.
I don't know. I've never heard him make that sound. 我不知道，我从没听过它发出那样的声音
Hey, you okay, pal?
Hey, you okay, pal? 嗨，老朋友，你还好吗？
Mom.
Mom. 妈妈？
Hey, you all right? You okay? Come on.
Hey, you all right? You okay? Come on. 嗨，你还好吗？ 没事吧，快点
Call the vet. The number's on the fridge. Tell him I'll be right there.
给兽医打电话 电话在电冰箱上，告诉他我马上到
Okay, don't you worry about a thing. I'll stay here and get everything cleaned up.
好的，你不用担心，我留在这 把这打扫干净
Thanks, Edie.
谢谢你, Edie
Is there anything I can do?
我有什么能帮上忙吗？
No.
不用
- Hey.
- 嗨
Hey.
嗨
How's Bongo doing?
Bongo怎么样了？
I'm, uh, just waiting to see if they'll have to operate.
呃，我等在这看看是否要做手术
Oh, god.
哦，天那
I-I... I stopped and I got this...
我，我停下来买了这个……
I am just so sorry for this.
我感到非常非常抱歉
I'm really sorry I snapped at you. I was ju so --
我真的很抱歉刚才对你发火 我只是……
Oh, no, it's okay.
哦，不用，没关系
Good news.
好消息
We won't have to do surgery.
不用做手术了
Oh, that's great.
哦，好极了
We've given Bongo something to help pass the earring.
我们给它吃点东西 帮它把耳环弄出来
When he does, would you like us to retrieve it for you?
弄出来之后 你需要我们把耳环还给你吗？
I'm going to say no.
不用了
Okay. You should be able to take him home in about an hour.
好的，一个小时左右你就能带它回家
You must be so relieved.
你一定觉得如释重负
I'm sorry. I was just really worried.
对不起，我只是真的很担心
Well, it was your dog. I get it.
当然，那是你的狗 我能理解
Actually, he was my wife's dog, and, uh...
事实上，那是我妻子的狗 呃……
one of the last things she said to me in the hospital before she died
她在医院里临死前 跟我说的最后一件事是
was to be sure I looked after him,
就是让我保证要好好照顾他
and, um, I promised her I would.
姆，我答应她我会的
And just like that,Susan could suddenly see something she'd never seen before.
就在那时，Susan突然看见了一点 她以前从未看到过的东西
He, uh, meant so much to her.
它，呃，对她来说非常重要
Mike Delfino was still in love with his late wife.
Mike Delfino仍然爱着他已故的妻子
And if, uh, something had happened, I would have felt like I had failed her.
如果，呃，如果它有什么不测 我感到好像让她失望了
I know that sounds stupid, but I...
我知道这听起来很愚蠢 但是我……
and she knew right then neither she nor Edie would be laying claim to his heart anytime soon.
她立即明白了 她和Edie谁也不能很快占据他的心
No, it doesn't. Not at all.
不，没有，一点也不
So she decided, for now,
所以她决定 从现在起
she could settle for just being his friend.
她仅仅做他的朋友就好了
This is for you. Well, for Bongo.
这个给你 是送给Bongo的
You give it to him.
你把这个给他
Yes. As I look back at the world I left behind,
是的。当我回头看看身后这个世界时
it's all so clear to me:
我看得如此的清晰
the beauty that waits to be unveiled,
有那么多有待发现的美丽
the mysteries that long to be uncovered.
和那么多有待揭幕的神秘
But people so rarely stop to take a look,
但人们很少会停下来看上一眼
they just keep moving.
他们只是不停的往前走
It's a shame really,
这真的很遗憾
there's so much to see.
有那么多值得一看的东西